{"data":[{"question":"There are a ban on smoking on the tube.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"on","c":"smoking","d":"on the tube","answer":"1","explain":"- Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"He cannot come to terms with the fact that he would never race again.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"come","b":"to","c":"with","d":"would","answer":"4","explain":"- Would-> will","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"People in Spain are very friendly with visitors and we weren't able to speak Spanish when we stayed there.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"with","c":"and","d":"when","answer":"3","explain":"- And-> although","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"The caf\u00e9 was in a mess and we have to do it up.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The caf\u00e9","b":"in a mess","c":"have to","d":"up","answer":"3","explain":"- Have to-> had to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"The last day of the holiday will ended in disaster.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The last day","b":"of the holiday","c":"will ended","d":"in disaster","answer":"3","explain":"- Will ended->will end","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"That dress has only the most slight mark on it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"That","b":"only","c":"the most slight","d":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- The most slight-> the slightest","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"My decision to get up and dance coincided with the band's decide to stop playing.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to get up","b":"with","c":"decide","d":"playing","answer":"3","explain":"- Decide-> decision","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"They were just as well as we had expected.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were","b":"just","c":"as well as","d":"had expected","answer":"3","explain":"- As well as-> as good as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"The minister's popular suffered as a result of the scandal.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"minister's","b":"popular","c":"as","d":"of","answer":"2","explain":"- Popular-> popularity","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"The teacher agreed introducing the new methods.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The teacher","b":"agreed","c":"introducing","d":"the new methods","answer":"3","explain":"- Introducing-> to introduce","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"}]}